# **Chris Heibel**

Software Engineer

### Profile

I'm a software engineer that thrives under pressure and have worked in many different fields from ski lodges to security and demolition. Those experiences made me realize that I wanted to make a career doing something I enjoy, building things.

## Experience

General Assembly Software Engineering Immersive, Denver, CO

June 2020 — September 2020

- Immersive Engineering program with 500+ hours of full stack experience.
- Worked on teams of 3-4 to develop React applications.
- Completed 4 projects in allotted time frame.
- Collaborated with other team members on projects and research.

## Projects

- Sick Spots, an application to guide you to new locations where you can ski, mountain bike, or just all around get out and enjoy yourself.
- DevSpot, a social media applications for developers.
- Peaks, an application to log peaks summited, and view others peak experiences.

## Employment History

Demolition at KCC concrete cutting, Wellington New Zealand

October 2019 — January 2020

Bouncer at WPS Security, Wanaka New Zealand

June 2019 — October 2020

Bouncer at Allied Security, Queenstown New Zealand

April 2019 — June 2019

Work the door while keeping collected in a high pressure environment.

Driver and Guest Services at Stoked Niseko, Niseko, Hokkaido, Japan

December 2018 — March 2019

Produce Clerk at Ridley's Family Market, Laramie, Wyoming

May 2017 — September 2018

## Education

**Economics, University of Wyoming** 

2016 - 2018

4 semesters

#### **Details**

Denver, 80204, USA, 719-225-6136 chrisheibel7@gmail.com

### Links

Github Linkedin Portfolio

lss555.github.io (portfolio)

#### **Skills**

JavaScript

HTML/CSS

MongoDB

Mongoose

jQuery

React

GitHub

RESTful API's

**Express** 

**PostgreSQL** 

Node.js

#### **Hobbies**

Skiing Gaming Travel